RYZHOV VITALIY

Frontend Developer

Kaluga, Russia

+7 (980) 082 07 89

eutyou@gmail.com

https://github.com/motorolla29

https://motorolla29.ru

Education

Moscow Institute of Humanities and Economics, Kaluga

Bachelor of Economics

2013 - 2017

Work experience

Kaluga Power Sale Company

Financial accounting department engineer

2018 - 2022

Freelancer, constant learner and code enthusiast

2022 - now

Summary

Since 2022, I have been engaged in web development of the client side of apps, learning to create responsive UX/UI with a deep design approach. I like to create beautiful things that are pleasant and convenient to use. To explore my skills in more detail, please visit my personal portfolio website https://motorolla29.ru

Technical skills

- HTML
- CSS/Sass, Bootstrap or similar CSS frameworks
- JavaScript
- Object-oriented programming
- React
- Redux
- Axios
- Jest, Enzyme, Chai
- GSAP, React Spring, Framer Motion
- Web graphic and animations with Canvas API
- Three.js
- SVG

Software and Tools

- Visual Studio Code
- NPM
- GIT
- Command Line basics
- GitHub
- Webpack/Gulp
- Babel
- ESLint | Prettier
- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Premiere
- Figma